{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 76 + 0?",
      "options": [
        73,
        76,
        85,
        84
      ],
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 19 + 1?",
      "options": [
        20,
        26,
        17,
        25
      ],
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 20 + 5?",
      "options": [
        27,
        22,
        28,
        25
      ],
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 90 + 0?",
      "options": [
        88,
        93,
        82,
        90
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 77 + 1?",
      "options": [
        79,
        78,
        71,
        73
      ],
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 80 + 2?",
      "options": [
        89,
        82,
        84,
        72
      ],
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 83 + 0?",
      "options": [
        83,
        92,
        75,
        79
      ],
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 40 + 4?",
      "options": [
        44,
        47,
        53,
        50
      ],
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 50 + 0?",
      "options": [
        53,
        52,
        50,
        47
      ],
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 47 + 2?",
      "options": [
        45,
        49,
        40,
        51
      ],
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 76 + 1?",
      "options": [
        87,
        81,
        78,
        77
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 41 + 1?",
      "options": [
        35,
        40,
        42,
        32
      ],
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 25 + 5?",
      "options": [
        30,
        38,
        32,
        26
      ],
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 46 + 1?",
      "options": [
        47,
        53,
        54,
        40
      ],
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 57 + 5?",
      "options": [
        62,
        68,
        66,
        55
      ],
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 60 + 0?",
      "options": [
        63,
        67,
        60,
        54
      ],
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 52 + 3?",
      "options": [
        63,
        52,
        61,
        55
      ],
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 87 + 0?",
      "options": [
        92,
        90,
        77,
        87
      ],
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 54 + 4?",
      "options": [
        60,
        65,
        62,
        58
      ],
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 38 + 1?",
      "options": [
        33,
        37,
        39,
        44
      ],
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 85 + 0?",
      "options": [
        95,
        90,
        86,
        85
      ],
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 10 + 3?",
      "options": [
        19,
        12,
        13,
        9
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 41 + 5?",
      "options": [
        46,
        41,
        37,
        55
      ],
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 94 + 1?",
      "options": [
        90,
        91,
        98,
        95
      ],
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 59 + 0?",
      "options": [
        54,
        59,
        65,
        55
      ],
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 64 + 5?",
      "options": [
        77,
        69,
        65,
        78
      ],
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 49 + 5?",
      "options": [
        63,
        54,
        59,
        61
      ],
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 70 + 2?",
      "options": [
        66,
        72,
        69,
        63
      ],
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 72 + 5?",
      "options": [
        80,
        83,
        70,
        77
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 49 + 4?",
      "options": [
        48,
        49,
        53,
        58
      ],
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 28 + 1?",
      "options": [
        31,
        29,
        33,
        21
      ],
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 55 + 2?",
      "options": [
        61,
        57,
        59,
        51
      ],
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 75 + 3?",
      "options": [
        78,
        68,
        74,
        80
      ],
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 58 + 4?",
      "options": [
        58,
        62,
        69,
        72
      ],
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 44 + 3?",
      "options": [
        47,
        57,
        52,
        53
      ],
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 78 + 4?",
      "options": [
        74,
        91,
        87,
        82
      ],
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 64 + 4?",
      "options": [
        67,
        77,
        68,
        69
      ],
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 62 + 0?",
      "options": [
        71,
        52,
        59,
        62
      ],
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 27 + 0?",
      "options": [
        20,
        25,
        27,
        35
      ],
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 73 + 0?",
      "options": [
        75,
        79,
        73,
        70
      ],
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 17 + 3?",
      "options": [
        14,
        28,
        20,
        30
      ],
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 22 + 2?",
      "options": [
        27,
        14,
        26,
        24
      ],
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 57 + 0?",
      "options": [
        50,
        51,
        57,
        47
      ],
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 66 + 2?",
      "options": [
        78,
        68,
        66,
        70
      ],
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 74 + 1?",
      "options": [
        84,
        75,
        85,
        76
      ],
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 55 + 0?",
      "options": [
        62,
        45,
        55,
        61
      ],
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 91 + 1?",
      "options": [
        86,
        92,
        93,
        90
      ],
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 79 + 1?",
      "options": [
        88,
        78,
        72,
        80
      ],
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 18 + 0?",
      "options": [
        26,
        23,
        12,
        18
      ],
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Level 4: What is 70 + 1?",
      "options": [
        71,
        78,
        72,
        64
      ],
      "answer": 71
    }
  ]
}